

+39 351 981 1639 nick.bertocco@gmail.com owsky.github.io San Donà di Piave, Italy

I'm a software developer who loves to tinker with modern programming languages and frameworks. I have both fullstack and mobile development working experience but my preferred role is **backend developer**. I'm currently attending a university course so I only consider part-time contracts.

#### **EDUCATION**

### University of Venice Bachelor of Computer Science

09 2018 - Present
Academic Excellence in Object
Oriented Programming,
Software Engineering and Web
Development

## University of Padua Master of Computer Science

09 2022 - Present Registration to be completed

### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

# Fullstack Developer @ Workteam

06 2022 - Present

Tasked with research and development of modern technologies with the goal to develop a new product

Designed and developed a web application with stack: Fastify, Svelte, MongoDB

Discovered and implemented/provided solutions for security issues concerning the company's main product

## Android Developer, Intern @ Cedacri Group

06 2021 - 09 2021

Handled compliance with the European regulation for accessibility in an indevelopment home banking Android application

Written internal documentation for Android development compliant with the platform's accessibility features

Curated the user experience for users with disabilities

### **PROFICIENCIES**



## **PROJECTS**

#### **Cinema but Fast**

Technologies:

Fastify, PostgreSQL, TypeScript

04 2022 - 06 2022

Restful API that serves both customers and admins of a cinema. Remake of a university project; it was originally developed using Flask and SQLAlchemy

#### **Connect Four**

Technologies:

TypeScript, Express.js, MongoDB,

Docker, Angular

06 2021 - 07 2021

Full stack application of the classic game Connect Four. It provides multiplayer and social features such as friends lists, game invites and spectating

#### SushiHub Redone

Technologies: Android, Kotlin

01 2021 - 03 2021

Android application that facilitates group ordering at a restaurant. P2P features powered by the Nearby technology allow local synchronization of the data